# PABLO DE JESÚS

## Full Stack Developer

pag753@gmail.com

<u>+52 1 238 133 60 66</u>

in linkedin.com/in/pag753

github.com/pag753

<u>Telegram</u>

pag753.000webhostapp.com



O



#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

Software engineer with more of two years of experience in the backend part and frontend using PHP technology and its Codeigniter and Yii2 frameworks. Participating in information management projects in databases. I am willing to learn more and use other technologies especially in JavaScript, Python and Ruby.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Full Stack Developer** 

Alphacredit

July 2020 - At present

Nodejs, Java and .Net Core developer in the company.

#### **Description**

Responsible for developing Node.js, Java and .Net Core processes in the company.

#### **Technologies used:**

Node.js









.Net Core

## **Full Stack Developer**

Grupo Salinas

March 2019 - June 2020

Java, Vue.js and Python full stack developer in the company.

#### **Description**

Responsible for developing REST services and web portals for the management of the company.

#### **Technologies used:**

Spring boot











(Vue.js

## **Full Stack Developer**

TecNM / Instituto Tecnológico de Tehuacán

September 2018 - December 2018

Responsible for full stack development and database of the module 'didactic instrumentation' for use by all teachers of the National Technological Institute of Mexico.

#### **Achievements:**

Before the teachers made the didactic instrumentation in programs such as "word", following specific standards and formats, but now:

- Filling data is fast, intuitive and effective.
- At the end of the capture the teachers obtain the didactic instrumentation in a PDF complying with the norms and formats required and the confidence that everything they wrote and saved is in a database.
- The document once generated can be consulted or edited on the platform when and where they want from a web browser and with an internet connection.

### **Technologies used:**















February 2018 - July 2018

Responsible for full stack development and database of platform for the management of laundry process in the company 'Lavados Especiales' from Puebla city.

## **Description**

Platform for automate in efficiently way the control of laundry processes and the company administration with the implementation of the project to obtain a better fastest and internal control.

## **Technologies used:**

PHP 7 Codeigniter MySQL jQuery HTML5 Bootstrap 4 Data Tables

## **SKILLS AND TOOLS**

Languajes
JavaScript
PHP
Python
Java
C / C++ / C#
Typescript
Frontend
jQuery
Bootstrap
HTML/CSS
Vue.js
Backend PHP Frameworks
Node.js
Python/Django
Java/Spring Boot
Others  AWS Docker Intellij Git FontAwesome Linux Jira

## **EDUCATION**

## **Computer Systems Enginer**

TecNM / Instituto Tecnológico de Tehuacán

2014 - 2018

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Microsoft Technology Associate**

Software Development Fundamentals

2015

### **Microsoft Technology Associate**

## **AWARDS**

## T State programming competition

In the <u>IT of Puebla</u> on April 22, 2016. Winner of the third place in the intermediate category.

## The National Student Event of Technological Innovation (ENEIT) 2016

National stage in the IT of Pachuca from 22 to 25 November 2016 by the project "Enerluz".

#### **TENEIT 2016**

Regional stage in IT of Gustavo A. Madero in Mexico City, from 20 to 23 September 2016 by the projects "Enerluz" and "Autosilla". Winner with "Enerluz" project.

## **LANGUAGE**

Spanish (Native)

English (Intermediate)

## **INTERESTS**

Reading

Swimming

Watching movies

## **VOLUNTEER**

**Full Time Missioner** 

Misioneros Servidores de la Palabra

April 2011 - September 2013